That's right.
So tell me,
don't you think
I'm the better
option now?
You just want
Ted for his money.
What makes you think
you have the right
to come
crawling back?
Bitch!
You'll pay for this!
Ted,
come back
to the Eagles,
I'll give you
whatever you want.
Name your price!
Appreciate the
offer, Henry, but...
I'm happy
with the Knights.
I think I'm gonna
stick around here
a while.
You sure, son?
Don't you want
to test yourself
on a bigger stage?
I've already
proven myself.
With this win,
with the Knights.
I don't need to
prove myself to
anyone anymore.
Damn it, this
is your fault!
You lost me
a top-tier player!
You know what,
you're done
with the Eagles!
Pack your shit and
get the fuck out!
Sir... Sir!
Please don't fire me!
Ted, I owe you...
A real apology.
Just come back
to the Eagles.
I lost our bet
fair and square.
So you can hit me...
if you want.
We'll just call even.
After, just come back.
Come back
to the Eagles.
Come on.
Hit me.
Fucking hit me, Ted.
I know
you want to.
how much you
fucking hate
me, Ted.
You saw me
fucking your wife,
remember that?
Fucking hit me!